Guide to the John B. Duncan papers, 1932-1989 MS2055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
John B. Duncan papers
1932-1989
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Duncan, John Bonner
MS2055
21 Linear Feet
In 1952, after twenty-eight years of service in city government, John Bonner Duncan (1910-1994) was appointed recorder of deeds for the District of Columbia. He served in this capacity until 1961, at which time President John F. Kennedy appointed him the first African-American commissioner of the District of Columbia. Collection contains photographs, speeches, awards, correspondence, medical records, articles, scrapbooks, memorabilia, and reference files. The material dates from 1932-89, although the bulk of the material dates from 1960-77. The material relates both to Duncan's personal life and to his professional career.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
John Duncan donated this collection to Gelman Library in 1991. Additional materials were donated by Duncan and Duncan's family in 1992, 1993, and 1994.
Biographical Note
In 1952, after twenty-eight years of service in city government, John Bonner Duncan (1910-1994) was appointed recorder of deeds for the District of Columbia. He served in this capacity until 1961, at which time President John F. Kennedy appointed him the first African-American commissioner of the District of Columbia. President Lyndon B. Johnson re-appointed him to this position in 1964. As a member of the city's last three-man board of commissioners, in 1967 Duncan advocated for the reinstatement of the city's present mayor-commission system.
In November 1967, Duncan was appointed assistant to the secretary of the U.S. Department of the Interior for Urban Relations. He retired from the government in 1969 and began a twenty-year career as a consultant in housing development, equal opportunity and public affairs groups.
He was active in nearly eighty civic organizations in the District of Columbia for forty years, including private and public agencies, which supported education, health, recreation, welfare, youth groups, human relations art and sciences. He was a supporter of religious organizations, civil rights groups and numerous service organizations.
John B. Duncan was born in Springfield, Kentucky in 1910. He received his bachelor of arts degree from Howard University, and graduated from Terrell Law School in 1938. He was a member of the Maryland Bar and an associate member of the Washington Bar Association. He served as an attorney and senior attorney for several federal agencies. Duncan married Edith West in 1938. They had two children, John Jr. and Joan. After the death of his first wife in 1966, Duncan married B. Delores Berry in 1969. Duncan passed away at his home in Alexandria, Virginia in 1994.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains photographs, speeches, awards, correspondence, medical records, articles, scrapbooks, memorabilia, and reference files. The material dates from 1932-89, although the bulk of the material dates from 1960-77. The material relates both to Duncan's personal life and to his professional career. There are many subjects within the reference files that represent topics of interest to Duncan while he was in office. These subjects include: legalized gambling, National Capital Downtown Committee, and minority integration into Boards in D.C. The speeches included in the collection are both speeches given by Duncan and also speeches he attended given by such people as Lyndon B. Johnson, Ralph Bunche, Roy Wilkins, Harle Selassie, A. Philip Randolph, and Patrick Cardinal O'Boyle. The scrapbooks in the collection span sixty years and begin with Duncan's early years in North Carolina and continuing until 1989.
Collection Organization
Organized into nine series: Photographs, Speeches, Correspondence, Honors and awards, Reference files, Personal files, Scrapbooks, Clippings, and Memorabilia.
Equal opportunity in employment; Scrapbooks; Gambling; Home rule; Photographs; Washington (D.C.); National Capital Downtown Committee (Washington, D.C.); O'Boyle, Patrick; Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip); Wilkins, Roy; District of Columbia. Office of the Recorder of Deeds; Duncan, John Bonner; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines); Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald); Bunche, Ralph J. (Ralph Johnson)
- Photographs, 1960-1968; MS2055 Series 1; 4.5 Linear feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of photographs. These images date from 1960-68. These images capture Duncan attending social and business functions, meeting U.S. government and local officials, distributing awards to program honorees and receiving honors for his distinguished service. Images show Duncan meeting and socializing with U.S. presidents, such as Truman, Kennedy, and Johnson. For example, in 1962 Duncan is photographed with President Johnson, s the chief executive congratulates him for winning the Big Brother of the Year award. Photographs of Eartha Kitt, an entertainer, visiting Duncan's office in 1963 and the 1965 Arbor Day Ceremony with Lady Bird Johnson are also in this collection. Protesters were photographed in Duncan's office in 1965 and during the same year, Duncan was photographed at the ceremony to rename the South Capital Street Bridge. Duncan was often photographed with retiring and newly appointed members of various commissioner's boards and is seen awarding "keys to the city" to numerous persons.
  - Photograph, Honorable Mention, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
  - Photograph, Duncan with President Truman and friends, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Swearing in of Peter Ridley, 1961 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Truckers Labor Day Safety Program, 1961 August 29 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife, greeting president of Peru, 1961 September (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Signing of contract, Helicopter Airways, 1961 September 08 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Business Women's Week, 1961 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, Operation Angel, 1961 September 27 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Men in costumes, District Building, 1961 October 09 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner at Budget Hearing, 1961 October 10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Industrial Safety Conference, 1961 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Department of Highways and Traffic Service Awards, 1961 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Department of Highways and Traffic Service Awards, 1961 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Groundbreaking, Infirmary and Admissions Building, 1961 October 24 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Proclamation of Candy Week, Duncan and Tobriner, 1961 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Youth Appreciation Week, 1961 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Presentation to Tobriner of Bangkok Flag and Bowl, 1961 December 15 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Groundbreaking of Doctors' Residence, DC General, 1962 January 08 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Civil Service Week, 1962 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Printing Week Luncheon, 1962 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Groundbreaking, Eugene Meyer School, 1962 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Duncan, Big Brother Award from Lyndon B. Johnson, 1962 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, American History Month, 1962 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, Award, Medical Society of DC, 1962 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Junior Commissioners, 1962 April 09 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Dedication Ceremony, Benning Branch Library, 1962 May 17 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Mayor of Somalia Receiving Key to City, 1962 May 23 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, National Negro Licensed Beverage Association Meeting, 1962 June (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Groundbreaking, W. Bruce Evans High School, 1962 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, C.A.C. Luncheon, 1962 July 11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Robert Kennedy and Commissioners, 1962 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, Ribbon Cutting, 1962 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Presentation of Key to Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1962 August 07 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Apprenticeship Council, 1962 August 08 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Fultz Quads, 1962 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Carlton Sickles and John F. Kennedy, 1962 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Duncan Receives Apprenticeship Stamp, 1962 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Presentation, Public Health Advisory Board, 1962 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Man at Table, 1962 September 25 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Presentation at DC Employees Fund Drive, 1962 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, JFK at Swearing in, 1962 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Swearing in of Dr. Grant, 1962 September 28 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Oath with Roderick Farrer, Board of Pharmacy, 1962 October 02 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Key to City to Mayor of Palermo, 1962 October 03 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, With William Nelson, DC Apprenticeship Council, 1962 October 05 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Credit Union Day, 1962 October 08 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Government Unit Kick Off with PM General, 1962 October 12 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Oath of Urban Renewal Council, Bertha Weinburg, 1962 October 23 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Awards ceremony, 1962 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Photograph, Duncan at League of Women Voter's Day, 1962 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Photograph, Veteran's Day Proclamation, 1962 November 08 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Photograph, Presentation to Nurses Board, 1962 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Photograph, Pre-Holiday Party, 1962 December (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Photograph, Bangkok Luncheon, 1962 December 06 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Bill of Rights Day, 1962 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Photograph, Duncan named Son of the Century, 1962 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Photograph, Shriner's Ball, 1962 December (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Photograph, Meeting, 1963 January 01 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Book Award, Mr. Sedgwick, 1963 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Civil Service Week, 1963 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Duncan with boy and woman, 1963 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Duncan with board members, 1963 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Meritorious Public Service Award, 1963 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two men, 1963 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Boy Scouts pinning of three commissioners, 1963 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Presenting check from VFW, 1963 February 08 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Proclamation for women Marines, 1963 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Meeting on Mental Health, 1963 February 15 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, American Banking, 1963 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group of men, 1963 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Duncan opening World Craft Exhibit, 1963 March 10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Giving key to Nyasaland and Malagasy Republic, 1963 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Speaking to National Health Forum, 1963 March 18 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Tobriner giving key to Mayor of Nairobi, Kenya, 1963 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, "Doctor's Day", 1963 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Presenting Cherry Blossom License Tags, 1963 March 27 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Duncan with unknown man, 1963 April (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Junior Commissioners Day, 1963 April 02 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Visit by Eartha Kitt, 1963 April 03 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Award, Gertrude Clarke Whittall, 1963 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two police officers, 1963 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group of teens, 1963 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Essay Merit Winner, 1963 May 07 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Duncan giving key to Don Romulo O'Farrill, 1963 May 07 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Armed Forces Day, 1963 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Swearing In of Group, 1963 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Portrait of Duncan, 1963 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Mayor of Zanzibar, 1963 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Speaker at South Carolina State College Convocation, 1963 June 02 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Cosmetology, 1963 June 04 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Swearing In, 1963 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Award to Public Welfare Advisory Committee on day care, 1963 June 20 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Health Welfare Council Award, 1963 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner with turbaned man, 1963 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Knights of Pythis Award, 1963 June 26 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, With two other commissioners at flag presentation, 1963 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, With two other commissioners and wives at Gala, 1963 June 27 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, Award to police, 1963 July 07 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Commissioners Dike and Tobriner, 1963 July 08 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, at table with three unidentified men, 1963 July 09 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Award, Public Health Advisory Council, 1963 July 15 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Presenting key to Dr. Adbul Zahir, Afghanistan, 1963 July 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Mrs. Fraction, 1963 July 18 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Man receiving Variety Clubs International Card, 1963 August (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two men, 1963 August (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Photograph, Georgetown University Forum, 1963 August 06 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Photograph, Presenting gift to foreign man, 1963 August 12 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Photograph, Duncan with man and woman receiving booklet, 1963 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Photograph, Award to retired member of Hospital Advisory Council, 1963 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Photograph, New members Council on Daycare, Circa 1963 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Photograph, Amy Hunt Presentation, Award, Superior Performance, 1963 August 26 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Photograph, Duncan Presentation, two men, 1963 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Photograph, Oath of office, Board of Appeals and Review, 1963 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Photograph, Duncan welcomes Mayor of Genoa, Italy, 1963 August 30 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Photograph, Swearing in new member of Board of Podiatry, 1963 September 06 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Photograph, Award for Superior Performance, 1963 September 09 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Credit Union Day, 1963 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Photograph, Oath of office, Board of Pharmacy, 1963 September 13 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Photograph, Appointed to Electrical Board, 1963 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Photograph, Retiring Award from Electrical Board, 1963 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Photograph, Retirement from Pharmacy Board, 1963 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Photograph, Retirement Award from Board of Pharmacy, 1963 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Photograph, Reception for Prime Minister of Ireland, 1963 October (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Photograph, New Members, Real Estate Board, 1963 October 01 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Photograph, New Members, Public Welfare Advisory Council, 1963 October 01 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Photograph, Duncan greeting diplomats, JFK and Jackie at station, 1963 October 01 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Photograph, Mini Lowenbrau keg, 1963 October 16 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Photograph, Retiring from Human Relations, Appeals and Review, 1963 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Photograph, Certificate to Nurses Examining Board, 1963 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Photograph, Duncan giving out award, 1963 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two men, 1963 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Photograph, Public Library winning award, 1963 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking with two men, 1963 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Bavarian Dance Club, 1963 October 26 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Photograph, Human Rights proclamation, 1963 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Photograph, Meritorious Public Service Award, 1963 November (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Merit, 1963 December 05 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Lena Horne and Detective Reed, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Anna Steen, DC Civic Association, 1964 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired member of Boxing Commission, 1964 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired member, Board of Appeals & Review, 1964 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, World's Fair Summer Festival Queen, 1964 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Sworn In member of Human Relations Council, 1964 February 03 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Oath of Board of Appeals and Review, 1964 February 03 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, New member, DC Apprenticeship Council, 1964 February 13 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Duncan gives key to man with Lyndon B. Johnson, 1964 March (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Duncan meeting with unknown man, 1964 March (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Boy Scout, 1964 March (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Swearing in new board member, 1964 March 02 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, National Symphony Month, 1964 March 02 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Unknown man outside ceremony, 1964 March 07 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Duncan swearing in Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1964 March 06 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Presentation of Cherry Blossom Festival tickets, 1964 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired Members, Hospital Advisory Board, 1964 March 23 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired Members, Board Examiners Veterinary, 1964 March 24 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Presentation of Mayor of Hamburg, Germany, 1964 April 03 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Junior Commissioners, 1964 April 06 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Air France inauguration, 1964 April 06 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Asian woman and monument, Cherry Blossom, 1964 April 07 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Award, 1964 June 09 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner with Argentinean Senators, 1964 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Coolidge High School, 1964 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Dedication of building, 1964 April 22 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Speaking at Department of Highways and Traffic, 1964 April 24 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Loyalty Day, 1964 April 30 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Give Award, 1964 May 04 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Presentation, 1964 May 04 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Speech, 1964 May 04 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Key to city, 1964 May 06 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Clean Air Week, 1964 May 14 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Plaque, Stewart Holland, 1963 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Presentation, Award to Mary Chatelain, 1964 June 02 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, JFK Playground, Robert Kennedy, 1964 June 03 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Oath, Committee on Employment of Handicapped, 1964 June 08 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Award, Janet Fay, Office of Handicapped, 1964 June 09 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Taras Shevchenko Day, 1964 June 24 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Duncan and three unknown men, 1964 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, Retired and new members of board, 1964 July 01 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Retired and new members of Recreation Board, 1964 July 16 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Tobriner, Miss USA and Miss Universe, 1964 August 10 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired member Traffic Board, 1964 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Duncan taking oath of office, 1964 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Duncan at President of DC Transit, Inc.'s house, 1964 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Duncan presents Distinguished Public Service Award, 1964 August 11 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Oath, Minimum Wage & Industrial Safety Board, 1964 August 13 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Photograph, Pan-American World Airways Banquet, 1964 August 14 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Photograph, Agreement signing, Potomac Interceptor System, 1964 August 18 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Photograph, Proclamation from Venezuelans to Tobriner, 1964 August 31 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Photograph, Duncan at opening of USDA Federal Campaign, 1964 September 09 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Photograph, Duncan visit to DC General, 1964 September 14 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Photograph, International Toastmaster and Town Crier, 1964 September 14-18 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Civic Responsibility Week, 1964 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Kenyan Minister of Public Works, 1964 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at meeting, 1964 September 28 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Photograph, Ad Club Kickoff Luncheon, 1964 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Photograph, Duncan presents gift to unknown man, 1964 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Pharmacy Week, 1964 September 30 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Photograph, 10th Annual One-Fund Drive, 1964 October 01 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Photograph, Receiving check, Nat'l Capital Housing Authority, 1964 October 01 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Photograph, Portrait of Hubert Humphrey, 1964 October 05 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Photograph, Award for Valor, Police and Fire Depts, 1964 October 06 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, American Education Week, 1964 October 09 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Photograph, With Lyndon Johnson, giving key to Pres. of Philippines, 1964 October 05 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Photograph, Retired ABC member, 1964 October 12 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Human Relations Council, 1964 October 13 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group of men, 1964 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Photograph, Duncan meets with women from NACWO, 1964 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife at voting building, 1964 November 03 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Human Rights Week, 1964 November 12 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Council on Higher Education, 1964 November 16 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Alcoholism Information Week, 1964 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Photograph, NCCJ Board of Trustees Meeting, 1964 November 22-23 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Photograph, Ceremony at Metropolitan Police #3, 1964 December 03 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Photograph, Award for retired members, Undertaker's Board, 1964 December 07 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Photograph, New members, Undertaker's Board, 1964 December 07 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Photograph, Unknown Party, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)